自らが王となるため 世界中に散らばった キメラアント達は
Something, will you forgive me for being a
各地で 暴虐の限りを尽くしていた
bad big brother? 'Kay.
被害の拡大を恐れた政府は
I...
ハンター協会に キメラアント討伐を依頼
love Killua.
ついに ハンター協会が立ち上がった
Don't make the same mistake. And you should apologize to Kite, not to me!
ハァ　ハァ…。
You didn't clearly say if he's dead or alive, but either way, you should apologize!
ハァ　ハァ…。 ハァ　ハァ…。
When apologizing to a friend, there's a rule. Do you know it?
ハァ…　うっ。 うぅ　あぁ…。
Huh? No, what is it?
ハァ　ハァ…　ヒィ。
You promise to do things differently next time.
ふぅ。
And you keep that promise, no matter what.
密入するのは　楽勝。
I wanted to give her an escape from that cycle.
けど　問題は　どうやって 敵の懐に潜り込むかだな。
I didn't know exactly how it all worked, but...
危ないかもしれないんでしょ？
I felt that if I let them capture her,
torture her, then kill her, the cycle would repeat itself.
「指組」？ ああ　敵国のスパイを 見つけたら報奨金。 革命の証拠をつかんだら報奨金。
A dull life in the middle of nowhere, but one lived in peace and quiet...
亡命の現場を押さえたら報奨金。
Until that life was suddenly ended
by mindless violence.
じゃあ　報奨金　欲しさに みんな必死に…。
I pulled the trigger
チクリポイントが 一定量を超えたら 組全員の階級が上がる。
with a prayer that she would escape that cycle.
逆に　虚偽の報告をしたり 組の中から犯罪者が出たら 全員が 厳罰を受けるってシステムだ。 アメとムチか…。
Regardless of my actions,
the Queen ate hundreds of humans.
かなり　たち悪いぜ。 家族は　みんなバラバラに 振り分けられるから。
And when they were reborn, only a few
could remember their prior lives.
組で結託して亡命しようにも 残りの家族が死刑か 良くても　終身投獄。
It's possible that most of the human
souls managed to safely escape.
家族での亡命は　途中で捕まれば 問答無用で死刑。
But I wanted to do something. I wanted to feel like I was helping them escape.
この国の一部特権階級の 飽食を満たすため 残りの国民は　ガリッガリ。 でも　「他の国では 半分以上の人間が １０歳までに餓死する」とか
If you're inside that body instead of her, that probably means she escaped, and I still haven't run into an Ant
テレビで 大ウソのニュース流すし…。 各国からの経済援助は 弱者に渡らず
who's told me I killed them in their prior life.
全部　車と宝石 ミサイルに変わる仕組み。
Perhaps they were all able to escape.
東ゴルトーへの経済支援史上 最大額を引き出すための 交渉の切り札っていわれている
Before all this happened, I didn't believe
in the human soul's existence.
核開発も 援助金でしてるって話だし。
I believed that humans had
おい！　爆発すんなよ！
the same worth as flies or fleas,
and that they only lived and then died.
な…　何とか大丈夫。
That the ego was nothing more
話　難しいんだもん。 でも　よく知ってるね　キルアは。
than a bug that arose because the human
brain was slightly more complex.
兄貴は多分 じいちゃんの受け売り。
That there was nothing after death.
じいちゃん？ ああ。 むかし　仕事で同じように 潜伏したことあんだってさ。
Our bodies simply decomposed,
turned to dust, and scattered.
ハンターの専用サイトでも 同じようなこと書いてあったし 今でも同じ制度を使ってる可能性 高いぜ。
I believed those tiny fragments had no purpose.
村だ。 ん…　小さいな。
My appearance is completely different, but I'm doing the same stupid things as before.
どうする？ 忍び込む。
It made me think.
そんなことして大丈夫？ 生の情報が欲しいんだ。
I may be a fool, but I won't deny
the things that I know now.
連中が着ている服とか
And I don't want to ignore the
things I don't understand.
階級を識別するバッジだとかは 一応　用意したけど 他にも　スパイを見分けるために
I died.
いろんな決まりが あるかもしれないから。
I died, and my body was broken into tiny pieces.
データは　いくらでも 集めておいたほうがいい。 ちょっと待ってて。
But that wasn't the end.
もぬけの殻だ。
And our DNA, which is even smaller, contains the vast amount of information that
comprises us, all within a double helix.
もう　みんな　首都のペイジンに 向かったのかな？ いや…　何かあったな。
And that infinitesimally small
size is a necessity for
それを隠している。 えっ？
the birth of the enormous space
known as the universe.
かなり雑なやり方でね。
Just because something is small does
not mean it produces less energy.
穴が浅くて 野犬に掘り返されたんだな。 恐らく　村人全員 ここに埋まってんな。 一体　どういうこと？ 国民大会の真の目的は　これだ。
I don't know what the future holds. So this is nothing more than
speculation on my part, but something inside told me that I
mustn't repeat the same things again.
町や村の人間が　ある日　突然 一斉に　いなくなっても
I'm guessing that I'm forced
to repeat all of this because
不自然じゃない状況。 選別は　もう始まってる。
there was something I failed to provide
my soul with while I was alive.
考えてみれば 全国民を集合させて 一気に選別するのは かなり大変だ。
You know how the body
何しろ　人口５００万人くらい いるんだから。
moves more slowly without
the soul's encouragement...
村単位　町単位で　少しずつ 処理して行ったほうがいい。
In my case, I've always been driven by the thought that I can't let things stay this way.
その場合　問題なのは 連絡がとれなくなって
I know it isn't right.
離れた家族や　仕事の仲間なんかが 騒ぎだすこと。 でも　国民大会って 大義名分があれば
I will repeat the cycle, while thinking that I have to change things.
その期間中は　長期不在を 誰も不思議だと思わない。
Because I made the wrong choice.
ケータイ所持厳禁の国だから
My target shouldn't have been that girl.
お互いに外出してるって 思わせれば 連絡がとれなくて当然の環境が 出来上がる。
It should have been the ones pursuing her.
選別が　すげぇスムーズに進むぜ。
It's no big deal.
首都のペイジンは 領土　南東の端にある。
It just means I was the biggest scumbag of all.
遠い地域から順に 選別して行けばいい算段。 各地域から首都への出発時間は 政府の指示で 直前に報告するとか言っとけば
The price for cleansing a tainted
soul was too heavy, so I avoided that.
地域同士で 事前に連絡をとり合って 動くこともできないから。 奴らにとって不都合な
While selfishly praying that her soul would escape, I was desperate to avoid getting hurt myself.
待ち合わせに来ないって状況を 防げるから 騒動の心配がないわけか。
I shot her to protect myself.
よく考えたら　５００万人を 殴って回るわけだよね　国中を。 ああ　仮に１％が生き残っても
And now, I'm trying to save myself again
by confessing my sins to you, the one who inherited her appearance.
５万人が奴らの兵隊になる計算だ。 そうじゃなくて　その前の話。 えっ？
Really...
いくら１０日… いや　あと９日あるとしても
I'm a hopeless case.
５００万人を期間内に 選別しようとしたら
I appreciate your listening to my story.
選別するほうも すごい人数がいるはずでしょ？
Wait. Don't run away.
１人の能力者が１０日間 １万人の国民を選別したとして え…。
You come with me.
うん…。
Forever.
５００人。 そう　そう！ 念能力を持つ兵隊アリが そんなに　たくさん いるはずがないってことか？
You'll stay with the person you shot, living life the only way you can.
うん。 俺も　そう思う。
This is your duty.
でも　多分　簡単。
You have no choice.
選別者が　念能力を使えなくても 別に　いいんだ。
No one will allow you to take your own life
えっ　何で？
and hit the reset button.
操ればいい。 あっ…。
You must live and apologize to me every day. I'll keep you so busy, you'll never have time
恐らく　あいつの能力…。
and do the work I tell you to do, as you devote your life to me.
単純なオート操作もできるし ゲンスルーみたく　相当数の人間を 同時に動かせるはず。 普通の人間でも オーラは出ているから
If you forget your current resolve and slip, I will kill you.
それを利用して　強制的に 拳へ　オーラを集中させて
So you can focus on living.
選別対象者を殴れば　容易に ５万人の即席軍隊が出来上がる。 ４９５万の屍の上にな。
Kite, you have a visitor. Let them in.
難を逃れた連中が　他の町や 村の様子を見に行くように
Kite?
仕向けるだけでいい。
Yeah.
本当の能力者じゃなく
Sorry.
操られてるだけの素人なら 抑えるのは楽勝だから どんどん倒して　動き回って 騒ぎを大きくする。
Come. Sit.
潜伏してたほうが絶対に有利だぞ。
Sorry for what?
やろう！ 選別が　すでに始まってるなら
I wasn't able to fight by your side.
黙って様子を見てるなんて 無理だよ。
I wasn't
うん！ ただし　俺１人でだ。
But...
えっ？ お前は潜め。 何でさ!?　だって ２人のほうが絶対…。
Next time, I'll protect you!
大事な目的を忘れんな！ あいつを倒すんだろ。 あっ…。 それだけを考えろ。
It sounds like you did some
crazy stuff to defeat Pitou. Yeah, I almost died...
他のことは　俺に任せとけ うまく　かき回すさ。 それに　お前には悪ぃが
However, that doesn't change the fact
that you defeated an enemy I couldn't.
これは 俺１人のほうが　やりやすい。
I suppose I can soothe my ego by telling myself
チェっ　分かったよ。
that my judgment was correct.
本当か？ えっ？ 本当に　分かったのかよ？
But I wouldn't be here now without
help from Killua and everyone else.
キルア…。
I didn't make it here by myself.
たとえ　目の前で 何人　人間が殺されてもだ！
It appears that we both needed more training.
俺のほうからメール入れる。
You should go back to him.
俺らのケータイは ここでも使えるはずだから。 キルア…。
I understand what you wanted to say.
悪い…　何でもねえよ。
I'm glad you came to see me.
ちょっと　ピリピリしてるだけだ。
If I need help, I promise to let you know.
何だ？
We're friends now.
こいつら ここの国の人間じゃないな
So right now, go back to Ging-san.
スパイにしてはガキだし… だが　強いな　まさか刺客か？
Okay.
歩く動作が　すでに半端ねえ
Sorry.
ポテンシャルは 師団長クラスか？
Sorry for what?
うっ…
I was trying to take the easy way out
by running away from everything.
気配を殺しきっても 何かを感じ取ったか
No matter the pain, I will keep living. So when I die, I'll feel I did the best I could.
ククク…。 好都合だぜ。
Ging!
私と家族を第三国へ 亡命させてくれる話は。 ご安心ください。
Yeah, he didn't say that he
would wait for me here...
我々の命にも かかわることなんでね。
It's huge!
「奴」と来たか… まるで他人事だな
This is definitely the tallest tree in the world.
奴の尻馬に乗った おこぼれじゃねえかよ 「奴」じゃなく　「我々」だろうが 小悪党！ ん？
The World Tree stands at the city's center, at a height of 1,784 meters.
分かってるよ ビジネスは　ビジネスだ では　マルコスさん
Humans are still unable to build a taller structure.
あなたは　普段通り 行動していればいい。 ２週間後には　家族と浜辺で のんびり過ごせますよ。
Climbing the tree is not forbidden, but you must pay a fee and sign a written agreement.
納得いかねえ。 このまま 人間が殴り殺されて行くのを
You can reach the 500-meter
point by elevator or stairs, but after that, you'll be risking your life.
黙って見てろってか？ 眠てぇのか!?　寝かすか!? あ　こら！ そう　興奮するな。
Every year, around 3,000
people attempt the climb, but 94% fail to reach the 1,000-meter
point, and turn back.
５００万の国民が １０日間で選別されるなら 単純計算で　１日５０万人！ 生き残るのは　恐らく１％！ それが？
Another 4% are forced to pay an extremely
pricey fee to be rescued from the tree, and another 1% fall and die.
すでに　４９万５０００人の人間が 殺されてるんだぞ！ 何で　てめぇは 落ち着いてられるんだ!?
Which means that, each year,
only about 30 people make it
ここで冷静さを失えば 何十億って人間が死ぬからだ。
to the top and return safely.
護衛軍の３匹を 王から離さなきゃ
So...
いかに会長でも王を倒せない。
This is as far as we're going.
そのためにも 事前に俺達の存在が
Yeah. Be careful.
奴らに知られるのは絶対にマズい。
Yeah.
今まで以上に 王の警護が厳重になるに 決まってるからだ。
Killua, thank you for everything. Yeah.
こらえろ。 全人類のため
Well, after you told me you would defeat Pitou alone
５００万人を 見捨てろっつうんだな！ そうだ。
and that it was none of my business, I was pretty depressed!
俺を責めて　気が済むなら そうしろよ。 だが代案も出さず
I'm really sorry...
正義面だけしたいってのは 虫が良過ぎないか？ うぅ…。
Brother! Well, you apologized.
クソ！
And I think I can say I'm only here with Alluka
now because of the time I spent with you.
その代わり　全力で
She's the one who healed you.
命を懸けてだ！
Huh?! Is that true?
ああ。
Why are you telling me now? You should have told me sooner!
大丈夫かな？　キルア
Come with me!
少し変だったけど… やっぱり一緒にいたほうが よかったんじゃないかな？
Alluka, can you tell Something to come out? Yeah.
よく逃げたな。
And I'm prepared to spend the
rest of my life protecting her.
フフっ…。
N-No way... I should be thanking you!
強じんな尻尾をバネにして 木々を縦横無尽に跳び回る！ 暗闇で俺の動きを 捕捉するのは不可能！
This is no good. If we stay here any longer... Yeah.
捕まえたぞ。 このまま　絞めつぶしてやるぜ！
I'll be traveling to all kinds of places with Alluka.
シャ！
I'll e-mail you from time to time. Me, too.
シャヒ!? 全然　絞まってないよ！
If anything comes up, let me know.
シャ…！
I'll do the same.
捕まったのは そっちだ！
Yeah, I will. Since you owe me a lot...
シャシャシャシャ！
Say hi to your dad for me. Yep.
ヘビの遺伝子を 継いでるみたいだから
And you haven't had a chance to talk alone yet. See you around.
最悪　１０日くらい絶食しても 死にはしないと思うけど。
After I've had my brother all to
myself for a while, I'll set him free.
思った通り　強いな。
Will you hang out with him then? Hold on! I'm the one choosing to hang out with him!
だが　もう少し観察が必要か。
Isn't she a great sister? Sorry, but as far as I'm concerned,
you're in second place.